{
    "subject": "resource/Conrad_Letzkau",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Assassinated_mayors",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Conrad Letzkau is Category:Assassinated mayors.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7130333185195923,
            "question": "Is there information available about Conrad Letzkau's life before his assassination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6745027303695679,
            "question": "What category does Conrad Letzkau belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6602613925933838,
            "question": "Why is Conrad Letzkau categorized as an 'assassinated mayor'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6443222761154175,
            "question": "Were there any consequences following the assassination of Conrad Letzkau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6324000358581543,
            "question": "What happened to Conrad Letzkau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4793914258480072,
            "question": "What tragic event occurred involving Conrad Letzkau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40566375851631165,
            "question": "What are some other examples of assassinated mayors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39632540941238403,
            "question": "Is Conrad Letzkau a historical figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37688472867012024,
            "question": "In what capacity was Conrad Letzkau known?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23703816533088684,
            "question": "Was Conrad Letzkau a mayor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Conrad Letzkau is Category:Assassinated mayors.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1236_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what capacity was Conrad Letzkau known?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1236_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Conrad Letzkau a historical figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1236_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other examples of assassinated mayors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1236_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1236_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context does not mention any assassinations or a category for assassinated mayors. The information provided discusses the mayoral terms and dates in Gda\u0144sk, Poland, but there is no reference to Conrad Letzkau being an assassinated mayor."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " Response: {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Conrad Letzkau (1405-1411) was a mayor of Danzig, but there is no evidence or information provided that suggests he was assassinated.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that Conrad Letzkau was a mayor of Gda\u0144sk from 1405 to 1411 and his tombstone is found in the main church's cemetery.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Conrad Letzkau is a mayor mentioned in the context information, but there is no indication that he was assassinated.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "There is no information suggesting that Conrad Letzkau was assassinated. The context provided details about the mayors of Gda\u0144sk, including their names and terms of office, but there is no mention of any assassination or violent death for him or any other mayor listed.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}